Hello hello how are you I have come to
talk to you about today's city product
I have come to take communication from you
which has been associated with you for a long time health insurance company
you have been pressing for so many years there are
some changes
when will you write about this so I have
reminded myself this first s nibha
health insurance company kar in fact email I am
from chief max bupa distraction
always energy and he says that max
bupa name has changed max parmeshwar
department change was in 2019 and
max snowboarder shoulder we fufa
sonika can't do bigg boss so that is why I have
reminded you get lemon health
insurance company so I
would like to tell you that you must have a lot of queries there has been a
lot of increase so WhatsApp
network policy holders under cycle
light how policy holder time
communicating each cell so I would
like to tell you that nothing is left
your policy time does acid test
from your product's teachers whatever
I have told you similar live acid test
partner hospital
's leader who method of sky element  Tired of
science, its management remains the same, what has been that
you, the biggest thing you have learned
from the hands of Korba Lever Company, in this way you will
start seeing updated changes in November-December, where
in the policy document there will be better
communication, there will be a mixture of Mysore Pak and lemon,
this test match, so you do
not need to do anything wrong,
just be a policy holder, you are in the right hand of
Shiva Reddy from Science and Research
Institute, so friends, request
companies, as I told you, there has been a change in the
company, so there was
no change for you, the company is
represented, so for a betterment,
we do not need anything like change,
sooner than inevitable, only for rent in
Hindi, old, so change happens for good,
I will tell you the name that
came, Nibhaav, which means marriage,
in space, this year first source of energy,
legs, source of positivity, spices, source
of hope, so with this I am doing,
Dilip is doing
and I have elaborated that your life
Like Suraj, I too understand Rohit and may your life be as
good as it is in the upcoming videos,
so while adding this, I just wanted to
tell you that we will meet soon, please specify and take
care of yourself.